http://www.fac-ette.com/our-privacy-policy

Our Privacy Policy
HomeAbout Us GemMaster IIGemMaster IIGemMaster II In ActionParts & ServicesContact Us
Register
Login
HomeReturn HomeAbout Us GemMaster IIGemMaster IIGemMaster II In ActionParts & ServicesContact Us
Search ...
Find
Privacy Policy
Print
Privacy Statement
This statement relates to our privacy practices in connection with this website. We are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of other websites. Any external links to other websites are clearly identifiable as such.
General Statement
Precision Faceting fully respects your right to privacy and will not collect any personal information about you on this website without your clear permission. Any personal information which you volunteer to the Commissioner will be treated with the highest standards of security and confidentiality, strictly in accordance with the Data Protection Acts, 1988 & 2003.
Collection and use of personal information
Precision Faceting does not collect any personal data about you on this website, apart from information which you volunteer (for example by emailing us using our online feedback form). Any information which you provide in this way is not made available to any third parties, and is used by the Commissioner only in line with the purpose for which you provided it. Your personal data may also be anonymised and used for statistical purposes.
Collection and use of technical information
Technical details in connection with visits to this website are logged for our statistical purposes. The technical details logged include the following items:
The IP address of your internet connection
The type of browser you are using
The date and time you accessed our site
The pages you have accessed and the documents downloaded
Precision Faceting will make no attempt to identify individual visitors, or to associate the technical details listed above with any individual. This information is used to allow us improve the information we are supplying to our users, find out how many people are visiting our sites and for statistical purposes. Some of the above information is used to create summary statistics which allow us to assess the number of visitors to the different sections of our site, discover what information is most and least used, inform us on future design and layout specifications, and help us make our site more user-friendly.
Precision Faceting may contact you using the information you supply. If you do not wish to be contacted, please contact me.
Correction of personal information
If you need to correct information you have supplied please contact us using the information on the Contact page.
Complaints about data processed via this website
If you are concerned about how personal data is processed via this website, please do not hesitate to bring such concerns to the attention of Precision Faceting.
Shopping Cart
0 Item(s)						 - $0.00
Your shopping cart is empty!
You are here:
Home
Our Privacy Policy
Quick
About Us
Our unwavering commitment to quality machining and customer satisfaction proved to be our keys to success; customers recognized our dedication to excellence....
Information
Terms & ConditionsOur Privacy PolicyReturns PolicySitemapTel: 1-859-757-5126
This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.
GemMaster
II
GemMaster II
The secret of the GemMaster accuracy is it's high quality components, electronic circuitry and craftsmanship, but also in unparalleled "standard" features. More...
Copyright © 2020.
Fac-ette GemMaster.
Forgot your username?
Forgot your password?
Fields marked with an asterisk (*) are required.
Register
Desktop Version
